computta.com 2019-10-24

# Privacy Policy | Computta.com

**Our Commitment To Online Privacy:** Your personal privacy is very important to Computta. To better protect your privacy, we provide this privacy policy notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

**Personal Information We Collect:** This privacy policy notice applies to all information collected on the Computta.com website. The types of personal information collected in the website are: email, IP address, your computer CPU and GPU types.

**How Your Personal Information Is Used:** Personally identifiable information collected by Computta.com will only be used strictly for the purpose of providing you with our service. We collect this information so that you will be able to access your account and reset the password in case of forgetting it. Moreover, we may sometimes send you email notifications in order to inform you about our software updates, website and program news and special deals and events available to our users. You can always unsubscribe from our email notification list and stop receiving any email communication from us.

We never use or share personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses if applicable.

**Links to 3rd party services:** Computta.com website may contain links to 3rd party services. However, you should be informed that we are not responsible for the privacy policy of those sites. Please, read through privacy statement of those 3rd party websites before sharing your personal information.
